{
    "id": "0b0c18b3aa9c430ab230b463efd33667",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The state of affairs …………………. sure to cause him anxiety.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "has",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "251a9048d4da438eaf611fa8a5b51f60"
        },
        {
            "question": "An advocate and a doctor ....................... on this street.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "lives",
                "are living"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3b35777f25c44b149db351c4a19349e1"
        },
        {
            "question": "The introduction of radical reforms ...................... opposed by the aristocracy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were",
                "has",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9b022969dc7e4584be12708bd44914eb"
        },
        {
            "question": "Slow and steady ………………….. the race.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "win",
                "wins",
                "is winning",
                "has won"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f2b7f291f50f4685880a70d464b49f43"
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………. hardly sat down when someone knocked at the door.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "had",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "01ddd355048a46e791a867e19cb96270"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has been working here ……………….. six years now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "from",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "157c2a8e591948b6a91ceb392e91a687"
        },
        {
            "question": "I saw him six months ..................... .",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "before",
                "ago",
                "past"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "27f9beb03807463e8205ab45e2fbac44"
        },
        {
            "question": "Were you foolish ……………….. to trust him?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "also",
                "as well",
                "enough"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "77df68745ee04cc981d0c55fc9983c55"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish you …………………. stop complaining like this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ef7d0bb752ad47f799ce3f17503954d8"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. you obey my instructions, you will be killed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Unless",
                "If",
                "Whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "301cac9b466d45b09576ea3ba3aaab80"
        }
    ]
}